A Guide to the Governor's Office, Executive Mansion Director, Records, 1973-1995
Library of Virginia
- Event Files 1982, 1986 (Box 1-3)
  - Robb Administration 1982-1986 (Box 1-2)
    - "Virginians for" Luncheon 1985 May 24 (Box 2, Folder 51)
    - Governor's Staff Party at Camp Pendleton 1985 May 27 (Box 2, Folder 52)
    - Contributors Reception 1985 May 28 (Box 2, Folder 53)
    - College Presidents' Luncheon 1985 June 3 (Box 2, Folder 54)
    - Cookout Honoring Cecil Carter, B.W. Pack, Frank White, and Sandy Bowen 1985 June 24 (Box 2, Folder 55)
    - Executive Mansion Donors' Reception 1985 June 25 (Box 2, Folder 56)
    - Electronic Data Systems (EDS) Luncheon 1985 July 19 (Box 2, Folder 57)
    - Current and Former Governor's Fellows Reunion, Camp Pendleton 1985 July 20 (Box 2, Folder 58)
    - Cocktail Party at Camp Pendleton 1985 July 20 (Box 2, Folder 59)
    - Farewell Luncheon for John Casteen 1985 July 29 (Box 2, Folder 60)
    - Clarinet Recital for Governor's Fellows 1985 July 29 (Box 2, Folder 61)
    - Governor's Economic Advisory Council Luncheon 1985 Aug 22 (Box 2, Folder 62)
    - Small Dinner Party Before "Sugar Babies" 1985 Aug 27 (Box 2, Folder 63)
    - Breakfast Honoring Dr. Joe Marchello 1985 Aug 30 (Box 2, Folder 64)
    - Hercules' Officials Luncheon 1985 Sept 5 (Box 2, Folder 65)
    - Brunch for Sarah Gayle and Jack Randolph 1985 Sept 22 (Box 2, Folder 66)
    - Bicentennial Commission for the U.S. Constitution Coffee 1985 Sept 23 (Box 2, Folder 67)
    - Virginia House Reception 1985 Sept 26 (Box 2, Folder 68)
    - Military Aides Reception 1985 Sept 27 (Box 2, Folder 69)
    - Mary Sue Terry Luncheon 1985 Sept 30 (Box 2, Folder 70)
    - Department of Economic Development (DED) Luncheon 1985 Oct 4 (Box 2, Folder 71)
    - Jerry Baliles Dinner and Cocktails 1985 Oct 19 (Box 2, Folder 72)
    - Governor's Regulatory Reform Advisory Board Coffee 1985 Oct 21 (Box 2, Folder 73)
    - Jerry Baliles Cocktails and Dinner 1985 Oct 21 (Box 2, Folder 74)
    - Virginia Board of Economists Luncheon 1985 Oct 25 (Box 2, Folder 75)
    - Dinner Party Honoring Lord and Lady Tollemasch 1985 Nov 4 (Box 2, Folder 76)
    - Election Night Dinner 1985 Nov 5 (Box 2, Folder 77)
    - Virginia Legislative Institute Reception 1985 Nov 19 (Box 2, Folder 78)
    - Robb, Richmond and Norfolk Boat Cruises 1985 Nov 20 & 23 (Box 2, Folder 79)
    - Fountain Dedication, Executive Mansion 1985 Dec 3 (Box 2, Folder 80)
    - Virginia Task Force on Infant Mortality Luncheon 1985 Dec 12 (Box 2, Folder 81)
    - Mansion Christmas Decorations 1985 (Box 2, Folder 82)
    - Tree Lighting Reception 1985 Dec 12 (Box 2, Folder 83)
    - Executive Mansion Christmas Open House 1985 Dec 13-15 (Box 2, Folder 84)
    - Party Honoring Margaret Bowlin 1985 Dec 13 (Box 2, Folder 85)
    - Hostesses Coffee 1985 Dec 17 (Box 2, Folder 86)
    - Virginia Association of Realtors Reception 1985 Dec 17 (Box 2, Folder 87)
    - Military Aides Reception 1985 Dec 17 (Box 2, Folder 88)
    - Christmas Staff Party 1985 Dec 19 (Box 2, Folder 89)
    - Christmas 1985 (Box 2, Folder 90)
    - Open House 1986 Jan 1 (Box 2, Folder 91)
    - End of Administration Gala 1986 Jan 4 (Box 2, Folder 92)
    - Agency Heads Luncheon 1986 Jan 7 (Box 2, Folder 93)
    - State of the Commonwealth Address Reception 1986 Jan 8 (Box 2, Folder 94)
    - Farewell Supper 1986 Jan 9 (Box 2, Folder 95)
  - Baliles Adminstration 1986-1990 (Box 2)
    Arranged chronologically by date. Contains correspondence, memos and notes concerning the preparations and arrangements made for events at the Executive Mansion during the Baliles Administration (1986-1990). This series includes guest lists and menus for many of the events. Also includes documentation on recurring events as well as some significant events during the Baliles Administration. These files do not reflect the complete entertaining activity of the Baliles administration.
    - Invitations - Names and Addresses 1986 (Box 2, Folder 96)
    - Executive Mansion Events 1986-1987 (Box 2, Folder 97)
    - Tree Lighting Reception 1986 Dec 12 (Box 2, Folder 98)
    - Christmas Open House 1986 Dec 13-15 (Box 2, Folder 99)
    - Garden Week 1987 Apr 21-25 (Box 2, Folder 100)
    - Mansion Christmas Decorations 1987 (Box 2, Folder 101)
    - Garden Week and Candlelight Tours 1988 Apr 26-30 (Box 2, Folder 102)
    - Mansion Christmas Decorations 1988 (Box 2, Folder 103)
    - Christmas Open House and Entertainment 1988 (Box 2, Folder 104)
    - Christmas Open House and Entertainment 1989 Sept 21 (Box 2, Folder 105)
    - Mansion Christmas Decorations 1989 (Box 2, Folder 106)
  - Wilder Administration 1990-1994 (Box 2-3)
    Arranged into two (2) subseries: Event Files, 1990-1994; and the Southern Governor's Association Meeting and African Trade Summit Files, 1992-1993.
    - Event Files 1990-1994 (Box 2-3)
      Arranged chronologically by date. Contains correspondence, memos and notes concerning the preparations and arrangements made for events at the Executive Mansion during the Wilder Administration (1990-1994). This series also includes guest lists and menus for many of the events. Also includes documentation on recurring and regular official events. These files, along with those in Library of Virginia accession 35539, give a more complete view of life in the Executive Mansion during the Wilder administration.
      - Entertainment 1990-1992 (Box 2, Folder 107)
      - Christmas Activities and Decorating 1990 (Box 2, Folder 108)
      - Tree Lighting Ceremony 1990 (Box 2, Folder 109)
      - Holiday Ornament Contest 1990 (Box 2, Folder 110)
      - Tree Lighting Ceremony Special Guests 1990 (Box 2, Folder 112)
      - Holiday Open House 1990 (Box 2, Folder 113)
      - Executive Mansion Open House 1990 Dec 14-16 (Box 2, Folder 114)
      - Garden Week 1990-1993 (Box 2, Folder 115)
      - Congressional Delegation Luncheon 1991 Jan 25 (Box 3, Folder 1)
      - General Assembly Black Caucus Breakfast 1991 Jan 31 (Box 3, Folder 2)
      - General Assembly Page's Breakfast 1991 Feb 14 (Box 3, Folder 3)
      - End of Session Reception for Legislators and Spouses 1991 Feb 20 (Box 3, Folder 4)
      - Christmas and Garden Week 1991 Apr 23-27 (Box 3, Folder 5)
      - Payment of Taxes Ceremony 1991 Nov 26 (Box 3, Folder 6)
      - Christmas Decorations 1991 (Box 3, Folder 7)
      - Christmas Entertainment 1991 (Box 3, Folder 8)
      - Mansion Tree Presentation 1991 Dec 3 (Box 3, Folder 9)
      - Tree Lighting Ceremony 1991 Dec 12 (Box 3, Folder 10)
      - Misc. Paperwork re: events 1992-1993 (Box 3, Folder 11)
      - Legislative Black Tie Receptions 1992 Jan 13-14 (Box 3, Folder 12)
      - Black Caucus Breakfast 1992 Jan 16 (Box 3, Folder 13)
      - Congressional Delegation Meeting and Luncheon 1992 Feb 7 (Box 3, Folder 14)
      - Pages Breakfast 1992 Feb 12 (Box 3, Folder 15)
      - Tea for General Assembly and Cabinet Spouses 1992 Feb 14 (Box 3, Folder 16)
      - End of Session Reception 1992 Mar 6 (Box 3, Folder 17)
      - Historic Garden Week 1992 Apr 18-26 (Box 3, Folder 18)
      - Payment of Taxes Ceremony 1992 Nov 18 (Box 3, Folder 19)
      - Virginia Christmas Tree Presentation 1992 Dec 3 (Box 3, Folder 20)
      - Tree Lighting Ceremony 1992 Dec 9 (Box 3, Folder 21)
      - Christmas Entertainment, Open House 1992 Dec 11-13 (Box 3, Folder 22)
      - End of Session Reception 1993 Jan 26 (Box 3, Folder 23)
      - Congressional Delegation Meeting and Luncheon 1993 Feb 7 (Box 3, Folder 24)
      - General Assembly Pages Breakfast 1993 Feb 17 (Box 3, Folder 25)
      - Black Caucus Breakfast 1993 Feb 18 (Box 3, Folder 26)
      - Black Tie Judiciary Reception 1993 June 15 (Box 3, Folder 27)
      - Governor's Fellows Buffet Dinner 1993 July 26 (Box 3, Folder 28)
      - Governor's Fellow Garden Supper 1993 June 29 (Box 3, Folder 29)
      - Howard University Luncheon 1993 Sept 10 (Box 3, Folder 30)
      - Payment of Taxes Ceremony 1993 Nov 17 (Box 3, Folder 31)
      - Holiday Tree Presentation 1993 Dec 3 (Box 3, Folder 32)
      - Tree Lighting Ceremony 1993 Dec 7 (Box 3, Folder 33)
      - End of Administration Reception 1994 Jan 12 (Box 3, Folder 34)
    - Southern Governor's Association Meeting and African Trade Summit 1992-1993 (Box 3)
      Arranged alphabetically by folder title. Contains correspondence, notes, and memoranda concerning the arrangements for the Southern Governor's Association Meeting. The meeting took place September 19- 21, 1993 in Richmond, Virginia. Coinciding with the meeting was a meeting with leaders of several African nations for the Southern Governor's Association African Trade Summit.
      Alphabetical
      - African Trade Summit - Budget 1992-1993 (Box 3, Folder 35)
      - African Trade Summit - Food 1992-1993 (Box 3, Folder 36)
      - African Trade Summit - Guest Lists 1992-1993 (Box 3, Folder 37)
      - African Trade Summit - Heads of State Dinner 1993 Sept 21 (Box 3, Folder 38)
      - African Trade Summit - Logistics 1992-1993 (Box 3, Folder 39)
      - African Trade Summit - Mansion Events 1992-1993 (Box 3, Folder 40)
      - African Trade Summit - Meeting with Ambassadors 1992-1993 (Box 3, Folder 41)
      - African Trade Summit - Meetings and Notes 1992-1993 (Box 3, Folder 42)
      - African Trade Summit - Operations Manual 1992-1993 (Box 3, Folder 43)
      - African Trade Summit - Setup 1992-1993 (Box 3, Folder 44)
      - African Trade Summit - Security/Transportation 1992-1993 (Box 3, Folder 45)
      - Southern Governor's Association Meeting - Budget 1992-1993 (Box 3, Folder 46)
      - Southern Governor's Association Meeting - Captiol Square Event 1992-1993 (Box 3, Folder 47)
      - Southern Governor's Association Meeting - Catering 1992-1993 (Box 3, Folder 48)
      - Southern Governor's Association Meeting - Entertainment/Activities 1992-1993 (Box 3, Folder 49)
      - Southern Governor's Association Meeting - Meetings and Notes 1992-1993 (Box 3, Folder 50)
      - Southern Governor's Association Meeting - Miscellaneous 1992-1993 (Box 3, Folder 51)
      - Southern Governor's Association Meeting - Operations Manual 1992-1993 (Box 3, Folder 52)
      - Southern Governor's Association Meeting - Press 1992-1993 (Box 3, Folder 53)
      - Southern Governor's Association Meeting - Security/Transportation 1992-1993 (Box 3, Folder 54)
      - Southern Governor's Association Meeting - Set-up/Tenting 1992-1993 (Box 3, Folder 55)
      - Southern Governor's Association: African Heads of States Event/Mansion Tours 1993 Sept 19 (Box 5, Folder 1)
  - Allen Adminstration 1994-1995 (Box 3)
    Arranged Chronologically by date. Contains memos and notes concerning the preparations and arrangements made for events at the Executive Mansion during the Allen Administration (1994-1998). These files, along with those in Library of Virginia accession 35875, give a more complete view of life in the Executive Mansion during the Allen administration.
    Chrological
    - Event Summary 1994 (Box 3, Folder 56)
    - Applause Unlimited Puppeteers 1994 (Box 3, Folder 57)
    - Historic Garden Week 1994 Apr 23-30 (Box 3, Folder 58)
    - Heritage Tourism Week Agenda for Susan Allen 1994 May 9-14 (Box 3, Folder 59)
    - Garden Week 1995 (Box 3, Folder 60)
  - Events spanning multiple administrations, or outside of gubernatorial functions 1982-1991 (Box 3)
    Arranged alphabetically by folder title. Contains memos and other materials regarding events that involved the residents of the Mansion, or spanned multiple administrations. Included are correspondence, notes, photographs (see notes), and other materials relating to these events.
    - Events not held at Mansion (Box 3, Folder 61)
    - Lynda J. Robb's Birthday Party 1982 Mar 19 (Box 3, Folder 62)
    - Cindy Robb's Birthday Party and Lunch 1982 Oct 22-24 (Box 3, Folder 63)
    - Halloween Parties 1982 Oct 30-31 (Box 3, Folder 64)
    - Robb Anniversary Party 1982 Dec 11 (Box 3, Folder 65)
    - Lynda J. Robb's Birthday Party 1983 Mar 18 (Box 3, Folder 66)
    - First Ladies Conference, Grand Rapids Michigan 1984 Apr 18-20 (Box 3, Folder 67)
    - Cindy Robb's Birthday Ball 1984 Oct 1984 (Box 3, Folder 68)
    - Party for Mrs. Johnson, Ian and Luci Turpin 1984 Dec 22 (Box 3, Folder 69)
    - First Ladies Mansion Fund 1982-1985 (Box 3, Folder 70)
    - Garden Week Correspondence 1982-1991 (Box 3, Folder 71)
    - Proclamation of L. Douglas Wilder Day, City of Newport News 1987 Oct 4 (Box 12, Folder 4)
    - Wedding favor from wedding of Loren Wilder and Edward James 1993 Apr 24 (Box 3, Folder 72)
- DGS/Special Projects Files 1981-1995 (Box 3-4)
  Arranged alphabetically by folder title. Contains correspondence, memos and other materials related to the special projects at the Mansion and relations with the Department of General Services. Of particular interest are materials relating to the renovations and improvement projects at the Mansion, including samples of materials used in the renovation and improvement projects. Also contains folders relating to the use of the Mansion by film crews for movies.
  - Auction Sale Notices 1992 (Box 3, Folder 73)
  - Asbestos Remodeling and Construction Project 1990 (Box 3, Folder 74)
  - Automatic Gate Opener 1993 (Box 3, Folder 75)
  - Basement Carpet 1992 (Box 3, Folder 76)
  - Basement Painting 1991 (Box 3, Folder 77)
  - Breezeway Renovation 1994 (Box 3, Folder 78)
  - Bureau of Facilities Management Survey of Agencies - Capitol Square 1993 (Box 3, Folder 79)
  - Carriage House Roof Replacement 1991 (Box 3, Folder 80)
  - Chimney Project 1990-1991 (Box 3, Folder 81)
  - Chimney Project 1990-1991 (Box 3, Folder 82)
  - Commission for the Preservation of the Capitol (Box 4, Folder 1)
  - Connecting Tunnel 1994 (Box 4, Folder 2)
  - Correspondence 1993-1989 (Box 4, Folder 3)
  - Cottage Repairs - Mansion (Box 4, Folder 4)
  - Emergency Lighting Installation 1991 (Box 12, Folder 5)
  - Executive Mansion Furnishings Changes, Repair and Cleaning 1990 (Box 4, Folder 5)
  - Filming: A Woman Named Jackie 1991 (Box 4, Folder 6)
  - Filming: A Woman Named Jackie 1991 (Box 4, Folder 7)
  - Filming: A Woman Named Jackie 1991 (Box 4, Folder 8)
  - Filming: Dream West 1985 (Box 4, Folder 9)
  - Filming: First Kid (Box 4, Folder 10)
  - Filming: Ironclads 1990-1991 (Box 4, Folder 11)
  - Filming: Shadow Conspiracy 1995 July 8-9 (Box 4, Folder 12)
  - Floor Plans, Executive Mansion 1987 (Box 4, Folder 13)
  - Furnishing and Redecorating Private Quarters 1990-1991 (Box 4, Folder 14)
  - Grounds - Executive Mansion 1971-1992 (Box 4, Folder 15)
  - Handicapped Access - Executive Mansion 1982-1991 (Box 4, Folder 16)
  - Handicapped Access Project 1991-1992 (Box 4, Folder 17)
  - Historical American Building Survey Team 1987 (Box 4, Folder 18)
  - Kitchen Improvements - Stove Replacement 1991-1992 (Box 4, Folder 19)
  - Long Range Improvement Planning Study for Use of the Executive Mansion (Box 4, Folder 20)
  - Long Range Improvement Planning Study for Use of the Executive Mansion (Box 4, Folder 21)
  - Mansion Gate House Air Conditioner 1991 (Box 4, Folder 22)
  - Mansion Kitchen Restoration 1982-1990 (Box 4, Folder 23)
  - Mansion Maintenance 1981-1988 (Box 4, Folder 24)
  - Mansion Tunnel Project 1994 (Box 4, Folder 25)
  - National Historic Landmark Application 1988 (Box 4, Folder 26)
  - New Fire and Security Alarm System Installation 1992 (Box 4, Folder 27)
  - Paint Analysis - Executive Mansion 1989 (Box 4, Folder 28)
  - Painting / Wallpaper of First Floor 1990 (Box 4, Folder 29)
  - Playground 1994 (Box 4, Folder 30)
  - Post Painting Work 1990 (Box 4, Folder 31)
  - Powder Room Wallpaper Replacement 1991 (Box 4, Folder 32)
  - "Project Streamline #27" 1991 (Box 4, Folder 33)
  - Recycling 1990-1991 (Box 4, Folder 34)
  - Remodeling of Dining Room Niches 1992 (Box 4, Folder 35)
  - Renovation Project Notes 1989-1990 (Box 4, Folder 36)
  - Renovation 1990 (Box 4, Folder 37)
  - Restoration - Executive Mansion 1987 (Box 4, Folder 38)
  - Roof Replacement and Exterior Painting (Box 4, Folder 39)
  - Virginia Film Office Location Requests 1992 (Box 4, Folder 40)
  - Wine Cellar (Box 4, Folder 41)
  - Wood Blinds and Ultraviolet Filtering Shades 1991-1992 (Box 4, Folder 42)
- Historic Attractions / Associations / Tourism 1984-1994 (Box 4-5)
  Arranged alphabetically by folder title. Contains correspondence, memos and other materials relating to Historic Attractions throughout the Richmond Area and the United States as well as information on tours given at the Mansion.
  - Bloemendal Newsletter (Louis Ginter Botanical Garden) 1990-1992 (Box 4, Folder 43)
  - Brochures - Historical Homes, etc. (Box 4, Folder 44)
  - Executive Mansion Summer Tours 1986 (Box 4, Folder 45)
  - Executive Mansion Summer Tours 1992 (Box 4, Folder 46)
  - Executive Mansion Tour Script - Revised March 1986 1986 (Box 4, Folder 47)
  - Executive Mansion Tour Hostess Manual, ca. 1993 1993 (Box 4, Folder 48)
  - Executive Mansions - Other States (Box 4, Folder 49)
  - Executive Mansions - Other States (Box 4, Folder 50)
  - Executive Mansions - Other States (Box 4, Folder 51)
  - Historic Homes (Box 4, Folder 52)
  - Hostess Orientation Workshop - Master Copy of Guidelines, etc. 1992 Feb 17 (Box 4, Folder 53)
  - Makeup Executive Mansion Tour Hostess Seminar 1992 Oct 19 (Box 4, Folder 54)
  - Mansion Hostesses (Box 4, Folder 55)
  - Master copies of Guidelines for Hostesses, Revisions, Additions 1991 Sept (Box 4, Folder 56)
  - New Trainees Hostess Information Forms 1993 Oct 7 (Box 4, Folder 57)
  - Questionnaires / Surveys (Box 4, Folder 58)
  - "Review of Evidence" G.S. Hood, Antiques Forum (Governor's Palace, Williamsburg) 1982 Jan 29 (Box 4, Folder 59)
  - Southern Governors Association: African Heads of State Event / Mansion Tours 1993 Sept 19 (Box 5, Folder 1)
  - Tours 1984-1991 (Box 5, Folder 2)
  - Tours: Information 1986-1989 (Box 5, Folder 3)
  - Tours - information: Quotations - Hostess Gifts (Box 5, Folder 4)
  - Tours 1994 Jan-Feb (Box 5, Folder 5)
  - Tours 1994 Mar-May (Box 5, Folder 6)
  - Tours 1994 June-Aug (Box 5, Folder 7)
  - Tours: Publicity 1988-1989 (Box 5, Folder 8)
  - Tours 1994 Sept-Dec (Box 5, Folder 9)
  - Tours (Box 5, Folder 10)
  - Virginia Association of Museums 1988-1994 (Box 5, Folder 11)
- Virginia Association of Museums (Box 5)
  Arranged alphabetically by folder title. Contains correspondence, memos, brochures, and other materials relating to the Executive Mansion and Capitol Square. Included in the series is information on specific aspects of the Mansion and its grounds.
  - Appraisal of Executive Mansion - Photographic Support 1980 Apr 30 (Box 12, Folder 7)
  - Appraisement of Personal Property Belonging to the Commonwealth of Virginia Executive Mansion 1980 Apr 30 (Box 12, Folder 8)
  - Brochures on the Mansion (Box 5, Folder 12)
  - Brochures (Mansion) (Box 5, Folder 13)
  - Capitol -200th Anniversary (Box 5, Folder 14)
  - Clippings (Box 5, Folder 15)
  - Clippings (Box 5, Folder 16)
  - Embossing - Ballroom Mantel Detail (Box 5, Folder 17)
  - Equipment Info./Insurance/Service Contracts/Warranties, Elevator 1989-1991 (Box 5, Folder 18)
  - "The Executive Mansion: Linwood Holton, Governor, Commonwealth of Virginia, 1970-1974" (Box 5, Folder 19)
  - Executive Mansion Inventory, Commonwealth of Virginia 1974 Jan 4 (Box 12, Folder 10)
  - Executive Mansion Inventory, Commonwealth of Virginia 1978 July 12 (Box 12, Folder 11)
  - Financial Information: Fixed Assets (Box 5, Folder 20)
  - Friends of Executive Mansion Brochures (Box 5, Folder 21)
  - Governor - Executive Office: Report on Audit for year ended June 30, 1984 (Box 5, Folder 22)
  - Governor - Executive Office: Report on Audit for year ended June 30, 1984 (Box 5, Folder 23)
  - Governor Wilder's Gift Stamp (for books) (Box 5, Folder 24)
  - Inventory of Personal Property Belonging to Commonwealth of Virginia Executive Mansion 1982 Apr 23 (Box 12, Folder 12)
  - Landscape Proposal - Tony Griffin 1994 (Box 5, Folder 25)
  - Mansion Misc. (Box 5, Folder 26)
  - Plants of the Executive Mansion 1983 (Box 5, Folder 27)
  - Policy Manual (Box 5, Folder 28)
  - Research Materials for restoration (Box 5, Folder 29)
  - State Capitol Diagrams (Box 5, Folder 30)
  - State Capitol Information (Box 5, Folder 31)
  - Stationary (Box 5, Folder 32)
  - Stationary Inventory (Box 5, Folder 33)
  - Stationary Samples / Inventory (Box 5, Folder 34)
  - Telephone Book Cover Artist: Vernon Johnson 1988 (Box 5, Folder 35)
  - "Virginia's Legendary Mansion" by Terry Morton 1994-1996 (Box 12, Folder 13)
  - Washington Statue - Capitol Square, Thomas Crawford, 1858 (Box 12, Folder 14)
- Citizens' Advisory Council on Furnishing and Interpreting the Executive Mansion 1973-1989 (Box 5-7)
  - Contributions 1973-1990 (Box 5-6)
    Arranged chronologically. Contains information regarding monetary and property donations made to the Citizens' Advisory Council on Furnishing and Interpreting the Executive Mansion for the calendar years 1973 through 1990. Members of the Citizens' Advisory Council on Furnishing and Interpreting the Executive Mansion transferred these files to the Office of the Director of the Executive Mansion in 1987. These materials compliment the materials found in the Library of Virginia accession 35652 from the Citizens' Advisory Council on Furnishing and Interpreting the Executive Mansion.
    - 1973 Mansion Contributions 1973 (Box 5, Folder 37)
    - 1973 Mansion Contributions 19 (Box 5, Folder 38)
    - 1974 Mansion Contributions 1974 (Box 5, Folder 39)
    - 1975 Mansion Contributions 1975 (Box 5, Folder 40)
    - 1976 Mansion Contributions 1976 (Box 5, Folder 41)
    - 1977 Mansion Contributions 1977 (Box 5, Folder 42)
    - 1978 Mansion Contributions 1978 (Box 5, Folder 43)
    - 1979 Mansion Contributions 1979 (Box 5, Folder 44)
    - Contributions, 1979-1990 1979-1980 (Box 5, Folder 45)
    - 1980 Mansion Contributions 1980 (Box 6, Folder 1)
    - 1981 Mansion Contributions 1981 (Box 6, Folder 2)
    - 1982 Mansion Contributions 1982 (Box 6, Folder 3)
    - 1983 Mansion Contributions 1983 (Box 6, Folder 4)
    - 1984 Mansion Contributions 1984 (Box 6, Folder 5)
    - 1985 Mansion Contributions 1985 (Box 6, Folder 6)
    - 1987 Mansion Contributions 1987 (Box 6, Folder 7)
    - 1988 Mansion Contributions 1988 (Box 6, Folder 8)
    - 1989 Mansion Contributions 1989 (Box 6, Folder 9)
  - Correspondence 1973-1989 (Box 6)
    Arranged chronologically. Contains correspondence and other materials relating to the Citizens' Advisory Council on Furnishing and Interpreting the Executive Mansion (formerly the Citizens' Advisory Committee on Furnishing and Interpreting the Executive Mansion). Included in these materials is correspondence regarding the donation and restoration of property for the furnishing of the Mansion as well as correspondence with members of the Citizens' Advisory Council. Members of the Citizens' Advisory Council on Furnishing and Interpreting the Executive Mansion transferred these files to the Office of the Director of the Executive Mansion in 1987. These materials compliment the materials found in the Library of Virginia accession 35652 from the Citizens' Advisory Council on Furnishing and Interpreting the Executive Mansion.
    - Notes from Ruth Anne M. Brooks and Notes re: Helen Scott Reed (Box 6, Folder 10)
    - Friends of the Executive Mansion, First "Friends" Reception by Mansion Committee (Box 6, Folder 11)
    - 1973 Correspondence 1973 (Box 6, Folder 12)
    - 1974 Correspondence 1974 (Box 6, Folder 13)
    - 1975 Correspondence 1975 (Box 6, Folder 14)
    - 1976 Correspondence 1976 (Box 6, Folder 15)
    - 1977 Correspondence 1977 (Box 6, Folder 16)
    - 1978 Correspondence 1978 (Box 6, Folder 17)
    - 1979 Correspondence 1979 (Box 6, Folder 18)
    - 1980 Correspondence 1980 (Box 6, Folder 19)
    - 1981 Correspondence 1981 (Box 6, Folder 20)